Finding Aid for the Daniel C. Prince Papers and S.T.A.R. Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Writings, Novels
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Hawaii, Daniel C. Prince, Draft Copies, incomplete (Box 49, File 10)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Hawaii, Daniel C. Prince, Draft, Mailed for copyright, May 21, 1979 (Box 49, File 11)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Hawaii, Daniel C. Prince, Draft Summary of Remaining Chapters, Chapters 5-18 (Box 49, File 12)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Hawaii, Daniel C. Prince, Summary of remaining chapters (Box 49, File 13)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Hawaii, Daniel C. Prince, Summary of Remaining Chapters, 8-23, Incomplete (Box 49, File 14)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Hawaii, Daniel C. Prince, Drafts, Handwritten (Box 49, File 15)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Hawaii, Daniel C. Prince, Drafts, Handwritten (Box 49, File 16)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Hawaii, Daniel C. Prince, Drafts, Handwritten (Box 49, File 17)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Hawaii, Daniel C. Prince, Drafts, Handwritten in spiral notebooks (Box 49, File 18)
- Writings, Novels
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Hawaii, Daniel C. Prince, Drafts, Handwritten in spiral notebook, and Fragment of unidentified story. (Box 50, File 1)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Materials (Box 50, File 2)
  - Writings, Novels—Nick Carter, Laser Earth Affair (Box 50, File 3)
  - Writings, Novels – Publishing Market Materials, including Correspondence (Box 50, File 4)
  - Writings, Novels—Ras Quel, After the Quake, Daniel C. Prince, Story Outline and Samples Chapters (Box 50, File 5)
  - Writings, Novels—Ras Quel, After the Quake, Daniel C. Prince, Mailed for Copyright, Mar 3, 1980 (Box 50, File 6)
  - Writings, Novels— Ras Quel, After the Quake, Daniel C. Prince, Mailed for Copyright, Apr 18, 1980 (Box 50, File 7)
- Publications
  - Miscellaneous Catalogues (Exhibition & Gallery) (Box 51, File 8)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 51, File 9)
  - New Art Examiner: Vol. 21, no. 10, Summer ’94; Vol. 22, no. 1, September ‘94 (Box 51, File 10)
  - Platinum: Vol. 1, no. 3, Jan/Feb. ‘94 (Box 51, File 11)
  - Raw Vision (Box 51, File 12)
  - Sotheby’s Auction Catalog, Jan. 17 and 19, 1997 (Box 51, File 13)
  - Vanderbilt Miscellaneous (Box 51, File 14)
  - Versus Vol. V No 1, Versus Vol. V No 2, Versus Vol. V No 3 (1972) (Box 51, File 15)
  - Versus Vol. V No 4, Versus Vol. V No 5, Versus Vol. V No 6 (1972) (Box 51, File 16)
  - Versus Vol. V No 8, Versus Vol. V No 9, Versus Vol. V No 10 (1972) (Box 51, File 17)
  - Versus Vol. V No 12, Versus Vol. V No 13, Versus Vol. V No 15 (1972) (Box 51, File 18)
- Publications
  - Versus Vol. VI No 17, Versus Vol. VI No 18, Versus Vol. VI No 20 (1973) (Box 51, File 1)
  - Versus Vol. VI No 21, Versus Vol. VI No 22, Versus Vol. VI No 25, Versus Vol. VI No 26 (1973) (Box 51, File 2)
  - Versus, Vol. 32, No.2 April ’97 (story on Dan Prince) (Box 51, File 3)
  - Versus, April 1997 (2) (Box 51, File 4)
  - Versus, Miscellaneous (Box 51, File 5)
  - Visions Art Quarterly, Summer, 1993 (Box 51, File 6)
  - Xpose: A Magazine of Art and Imagination (Box 51, File 7)
- Personal and Biographical
  - Assorted (Box 51, File 8)
  - Clippings on Dan Prince and Artwork (Box 51, File 9)
  - Passports and Birth Certificate (Box 51, File 10)
  - Resumes- Complete Artist’s Resume (Box 51, File 11)
  - Resumes- Complete Business Resume (Box 51, File 12)
  - Resumes- Incomplete Resumes (Box 51, File 13)
  - Resumes- Resumes and Cover Letters (Box 51, File 14)
  - Resumes- Listings of Dan Prince’s Artworks 1970’s and 1980’s (Box 51, File 15)
  - Trip to Italy- Maps, Gallery Guides, and Guide to Florence (Box 51, File 16)
  - Trip to Italy- Memorabilia (Box 51, File 17)
  - Trip to Italy- Photos (Box 51, File 18)
  - Trip to Italy- Scrapbook (Box 51, File 19)
  - Vanderbilt University Diploma (Box 51, File 20)
- Ethnographic Arts
  - Ethnographic Arts, Publications – Artes de Mexico, Ano XIX, No. 160 and 161 (Box 52, File 1)
  - Ethnographic Arts, Publications – artscanada, Dec. 1973/ Jan. 1974 (Box 52, File 2)
  - Ethnographic Arts, Publications – The Huichol Creation of the World, E. B. Crocker Art Gallery 1975 Essay and Catalogue by Juan Negrin (Box 52, File 3)
  - Ethnographic Arts, Publications – Mexican Native Arts and Crafts by Luis Covarrubias (Box 52, File 4)
  - Ethnographic Arts, Publications – Myth in Art: A Huichol Depicts His Reality by Peter T. Furst (Box 52, File 5)
  - Ethnographic Arts, Publications – National Geographic June 1977 Vol. 151, no 6. Mexico’s People of Myth and Magic (Box 52, File 6)
  - Ethnographic Arts, Publications – Ojos de Dios What They Are…How to Make Them, By Evelyn Ely (Box 52, File 7)
  - Ethnographic Arts, Publications – Peyote Hunt The Sacred Journey of the Huichol Indians By Barbara G. Myerhoff (Box 52, File 8)
  - Ethnographic Arts, Subject Files –African (Box 52, File 9)
  - Ethnographic Arts, Subject Files –American Rock Art Research Association (Box 52, File 10)
  - Ethnographic Arts, Subject Files –American Rock Art Research Association, La Pintura Newsletter 1988-1993 Incomplete (Box 52, File 11)
  - Ethnographic Arts, Subject Files –Asia and South Pacific (Box 52, File 12)
  - Ethnographic Arts, Subject Files –Central and South America (Box 52, File 13)
  - Ethnographic Arts, Subject Files –Europe (Box 52, File 14)
  - Ethnographic Arts, Subject Files –General (Box 52, File 15)
- Ethnographic Arts
  - Ethnographic Arts, Subject Files - Huichol Indians (Box 53, File 1)
  - Ethnographic Arts, Subject Files - Huichol - Correspondence and General Materials (Box 53, File 2)
  - Ethnographic Arts, Subject Files - Inuit (Box 53, File 3)
  - Ethnographic Arts, Subject Files - Native American Indian (Box 53, File 4)
  - Ethnographic Arts, Subject Files - North American Religious Groups (Amish, Mennonite, Shaker) (Box 53, File 5)
  - Ethnographic Arts, Subject Files - Petroglyphs (Box 53, File 6)
- Subject Files
  - Subject Files—Addresses (Box 53, File 7)
  - Subject Files—Architecture and Buildings (Box 53, File 8)
  - Subject Files—Art Clippings, undated (Box 53, File 9)
  - Clippings - Art, 1971-1994 (Box 53, File 10)
  - Clippings - Art, 1995-1999 (Box 53, File 11)
  - Clippings - Art, 2000 (Box 53, File 12)
  - Clippings - Art, 2000 (Box 53, File 13)
  - Subject Files—Artist Biographies (Box 53, File 14)
- Subject Files
  - Subject Files—Bed and Breakfasts (Box 54, File 1)
  - Subject Files—Bibliographies (Box 54, File 2)
  - Subject Files, Business—Blakemore Apartment Building, Clippings (Box 54, File 3)
  - Subject Files—Books (Box 54, File 4)
  - Subject Files—Brain Research (Box 54, File 5)
  - Subject Files—Burish, Thomas G.; Cancer and Chemotherapy articles (Box 54, File 6)
  - Subject Files, Business—General Clippings (Box 54, File 7)
  - Subject Files, Business—Computer and Technology, Clippings (Box 54, File 8)
  - Subject Files, Business—Landmark Square, Clippings (Box 54, File 9)
  - Subject Files—Censorship and Related Topics (Box 54, File 10)
  - Subject Files—Children’s Art (Box 54, File 11)
  - Subject Files—Children ‘s Art (Box 54, File 12)
  - Subject Files—Children ‘s Art, Emmett Yokley, Jr. Notebooks (Box 54, File 13)
  - Subject Files—Circus (Box 54, File 14)
  - Subject Files—Collector’s and Collecting (Box 54, File 15)
  - Subject Files—Cooks (Box 54, File 16)
- Subject Files
  - Subject Files—Cuz’s Uptown Barbeque (Box 55, File 1)
  - Subject Files—Death and the Day of the Deed (Box 55, File 2)
  - Subject Files—Design Motifs (Box 55, File 3)
  - Subject Files—Diners (Box 55, File 4)
  - Subject Files—Disabilities (Box 55, File 5)
  - Subject Files—Education (Box 55, File 6)
  - Subject Files—Elderly Art (Box 55, File 7)
  - Subject Files—Elgin Marbles (Box 55, File 8)
  - Subject Files—Elvis Lyrics (Box 55, File 9)
  - Subject Files—Feng Shui (Box 55, File 10)
  - Subject Files—Festivals, Events, and Happenings (Box 55, File 11)
  - Subject Files—Folkart, Antique Dealers and Auctions (Box 55, File 12)
  - Subject Files—Folkart, Assorted Academic Writings (Box 55, File 13)
  - Subject Files—Folkart, Assorted Clippings on Folkart in General (Box 55, File 14)
  - Subject Files—Folkart, Assorted Magazine Articles (Box 55, File 15)
  - Subject Files—Folkart, Assorted Folkart Media and Styles (Box 55, File 16)
  - Subject Files—Folkart, Black Arts (Box 55, File 17)
  - Subject Files—Folkart, Carousels (Box 55, File 18)
  - Subject Files—Folkart, Decoys (Box 55, File 19)
  - Subject Files—Folkart, Furniture (Box 55, File 20)
  - Subject Files—Folkart, Scrimshaw and Whaling (Box 55, File 21)
  - Subject Files—Folkart, Sea Shells (Box 55, File 22)
  - Subject Files—Folkart, Textiles (Box 55, File 23)
  - Subject Files—Folkart, Tombstones and Graveyards (Box 55, File 24)
  - Subject Files—Folkart, Toys (Box 55, File 25)
  - Subject Files—Folkart, Whily-gigs (Box 55, File 26)
- Subject Files
  - Subject Files—Found Object (Box 56, File 1)
  - Subject Files—Furniture (Box 56, File 2)
  - Subject Files—Futurist or Pop Art (Box 56, File 3)
  - Subject Files—Graffiti and Street Art (Box 56, File 4)
  - Subject Files—John Hiatt Video (Box 56, File 5)
  - Subject Files—Individuals, A - C (Box 56, File 6)
  - Subject Files—Individuals, D - F (Box 56, File 7)
  - Subject Files—Individuals, G - J (Box 56, File 8)
  - Subject Files—Individuals, K - N (Box 56, File 9)
  - Subject Files—Individuals, O - R (Box 56, File 10)
  - Subject Files—Individuals, S - Z (Box 56, File 11)
  - Subject Files—Inventors (Box 56, File 12)
  - Subject Files—Jail Art (Box 56, File 13)
  - Subject Files—L.A. Art (Box 56, File 14)
  - Subject Files—Large Contemporary Issues (Box 56, File 15)
  - Subject Files—Libraries and Archives (Box 56, File 16)
  - Subject Files—Light/Saraf Films (Box 56, File 17)
  - Subject Files—Magicians (Box 56, File 18)
  - Subject Files—Major Artists (Box 56, File 19)
  - Subject Files—Mentally Handicapped Artists (Box 56, File 20)
  - Subject Files—Medical (Box 56, File 21)
  - Subject Files—Miniature Golf (Box 56, File 22)
  - Subject Files—Miscellaneous Clippings (Box 56, File 23)
  - Subject Files—Murals (Box 56, File 24)
- Subject Files
  - Subject Files—Musicians (Box 57, File 1)
  - Subject Files—Mystic, Connecticut (Box 57, File 2)
  - Subject Files—Non-Visual Types of Self-Taught art (Box 57, File 3)
  - Subject Files—Optics/Perception (and the brain) (Box 57, File 4)
  - Subject Files, Other Authors—The Job, Josiah Bridge (Box 57, File 5)
  - Subject Files, Other Authors—Talking About History, Alexander Marchant, preface and Chapters 1 - 3 (Box 57, File 6)
  - Subject Files, Other Authors—Talking About History, Alexander Marchant, Chapters 4-6 (Box 57, File 7)
  - Subject Files, Other Authors—Talking About History, Alexander Marchant, Chapters 7-9 (Box 57, File 8)
  - Subject Files, Other Authors—Talking About History, Alexander Marchant, Chapters 10-12 (Box 57, File 9)
  - Subject Files, Other Authors—Talking About History, Alexander Marchant, Chapters 13-15 (Box 57, File 10)
  - Subject Files, Outsider Art - Assorted (Box 57, File 11)
  - Subject Files, Outsider Art - Magazine Articles (Box 57, File 12)
  - Subject Files, Outsider Art - Newspaper Clippings (Box 57, File 13)
  - Subject Files - Physically Handicapped Artists (Box 57, File 14)
  - Subject Files - Potters and Ceramics (Box 57, File 15)
  - Subject Files - Primm Springs, TN (Box 57, File 16)
  - Subject Files - Primm Springs, TN, clippings on Resorts, Retreats, Spas, and Hot Springs (Box 57, File 17)
- Subject Files
  - Subject File, Projects – Emergency School Aid Act- West Jackson Elementary School Jackson, TN- Alphabet Soup (Box 58, File 1)
  - Subject Files, Projects – North Carolina Artist Colony Prospect (Box 58, File 2)
  - Subject Files, Projects – Old Town Hall, Stamford, Connecticut (Box 58, File 3)
  - Subject Files, Projects – Southend Foundation, Inc. (Box 58, File 4)
  - Subject Files, Projects – Southend Neighborhood Association Minutes 9 Sep 1987- 13 May 1989. Southend Foundation, Inc. Minutes 17 May 1989-17 Jan 1990 (Box 58, File 5)
  - Subject Files, Projects – Southend Foundation, Inc. Southend Community Center Summer Arts Program 1988-1989 (Box 58, File 6)
  - Subject Files, Projects – Follow-up Projects to the Southend Community Center Summer Arts Program and United Way Mural 1988 (Box 58, File 7)
  - Subject Files, Projects – Southend Community (Box 58, File 8)
  - Subject Files, Projects – Stamford, Connecticut, Water Pollution Control Facility (Box 58, File 9)
  - Subject Files – Public Art Clippings (Box 58, File 10)
  - Subject Files – Public Relations Materials (Box 58, File 11)
  - Subject Files – Roadside Art (Box 58, File 12)
  - Subject Files – Screen Painting (Box 58, File 13)
  - Subject Files – Sculpture (Box 58, File 14)
  - Subject Files – Self-taught, general (Box 58, File 15)
  - Subject Files – Shrines (Box 58, File 16)
  - Subject Files – Signs (Box 58, File 17)
  - Subject Files – Social Concerns in Self-Taught Art, Sept. 11, 2001 (Box 58, File 18)
  - Subject Files – South Pacific (Box 58, File 19)
  - Subject Files – Surrealism and Dada Art (Box 58, File 20)
  - Subject Files – Technology, Web, and the Television & Film industries (Box 58, File 21)
  - Subject Files – Transportation (Box 58, File 22)
  - Subject Files – Travel Clippings (Box 58, File 23)
- Subject Files
  - Subject Files – Vanderbilt Family (Box 59, File 1)
  - Subject Files – Vanderbilt University; Humanities/Liberal Studies 201 class pack (Box 59, File 2)
  - Subject Files – Vanderbilt University Materials (Box 59, File 3)
  - Subject Files – Writers (Box 59, File 4)
- Oversized Materials
  - Oversized Materials – Artist Files – Fred George (Box 60, File 1)
  - Oversized Materials – Artist Files – William Laga (Box 60, File 2)
  - Oversized Materials – Artist Files – Dan Prince, Clippings, November 12, 1976- April 7, 1977 (Box 60, File 3)
  - Oversized Materials – Artist Files – Dan Prince, Clippings, August 13, 1977- November 3, 1985 (Box 60, File 4)
  - Oversized Materials – Artist Files – Dan Prince, Clippings Winter, 1987- August 19, 1992, and Undated (Box 60, File 5)
  - Oversized Materials – Artist Files – Dan Prince, Clippings, Murals- Helping to Help (Box 60, File 6)
  - Oversized Materials – Artist Files – Dan Prince, Clippings, Murals- Life in America (Box 60, File 7)
  - Oversized Materials – Artist Files – Dan Prince, Clippings, Murals- Sight of Music (Box 60, File 8)
  - Oversized Materials – Artist Files – Dan Prince, Collage (Box 60, File 9)
  - Oversized Materials – Artist Files – Dan Prince, Ripley’s Believe It or Not Series Materials (Box 60, File 10)
  - Oversized Materials – Artist Files – Bernard Schatz (L-15) (Box 60, File 11)
  - Oversized Materials – Artist Files – Robert E. Smith (Box 60, File 12)
  - Oversized Materials – Artist Files – Rhawn York (Box 60, File 13)
  - Oversized Materials – Environments – John Greco, Holyland USA (Box 60, File 14)
  - Oversized Materials – Organizations and Events, Exhibits – A Good Likeness (Box 60, File 15)
  - Oversized Materials – Organizations and Events, Exhibits – A Hand Has Five Fingers (Box 60, File 16)
  - Oversized Materials – Organizations and Events, Exhibits – The Biggest (Box 60, File 17)
  - Oversized Materials – Organizations and Events, Exhibits – California Discoveries (Box 60, File 18)
  - Oversized Materials – Organizations and Events, Exhibits – Flights of Fancy (Box 60, File 19)
  - Oversized Materials – Organizations and Events, Exhibits – Rebuilding Liberty (Box 60, File 20)
  - Oversized Materials – Organizations and Events – St. Sophie’s (Box 60, File 21)
- Oversized Materials
  - Oversized Materials – Writings, Manuscripts- Passing in the Outsider Lane, Page Proofs, Chapters 1-5 (Box 61, File 1)
  - Oversized Materials – Writings, Manuscripts- Passing in the Outsider Lane, Page Proofs, Chapters 6-11 (Box 61, File 2)
  - Oversized Materials – Writings, Manuscripts- Passing in the Outsider Lane, Page Proofs, Chapters 12-17 (Box 61, File 3)
  - Oversized Materials – Writings, Manuscripts- Passing in the Outsider Lane, Page Proofs, Chapters 18-21 (Box 61, File 4)
  - Oversized Materials – Writings, Manuscripts- Passing in the Outsider Lane, Page Proofs, Complete Set (Box 61, File 5)
  - Oversized Materials – Writings, Manuscripts- Passing in the Outsider Lane, Page Proofs, Miscellaneous (Box 61, File 6)
  - Oversized Materials – Writings, Manuscripts- Passing in the Outsider Lane, Page Proofs, Miscellaneous (Box 61, File 7)
  - Oversized Materials – Writings, Manuscripts- Passing in the Outsider Lane, Page Proofs, Color Proofs (Box 61, File 8)
  - Oversized Materials – Writings, Manuscripts- Passing in the Outsider Lane, Publicity (Box 61, File 9)
  - Oversized Materials – Publications- Number (No 39 Visionary Arts Issue Vol. 15 No 1 2001) (Box 61, File 10)
  - Oversized Materials – Publications – Versus – Miscellaneous Artwork and Mock-ups (Box 61, File 11)
  - Oversized Materials – Subject Files, Outsider Art- Newspaper Clippings, May 16, 1991 (Box 61, File 12)
  - Oversized Materials – Subject Files, Projects- CETA Programs, Committee on Trainin1g and Employment 1979 Stamford, CT, Newspaper Clippings, August 16 and 17, 1979 (Box 61, File 13)
  - Oversized Materials – Subject Files, Projects- Emergency School Aid Act 1981, West Jackson Elementary School, Jackson, TN, Alphabet Soup (Box 61, File 14)
  - Oversized Materials – Subject Files, Projects- Southend Environmental Arts Program, Newspaper Clippings, August 18 and 25, 1988, September 1 and 4, 1988 (Box 61, File 15)
- Photographs
  - (Box 62)
    - JRA (Box A)
    - Acuff, Roy Neil (Box A)
    - Aiken, Gayleen (Box A)
    - Almon, LeRoy (Box A)
    - Ambrose, Anne (Box A)
    - Armatis, Michael (Box A)
    - Armistead, Larry (Box A)
  - (Box 62)
    - Armistead, Larry (cont.) (Box B)
    - Asserfea, Indra (Box B)
    - Auslender, Stephen (Box B)
    - Backus, Madison (Box B)
    - Baeder, John (Box B)
    - Bajaj, Bindu (Box B)
    - Bannister, Bradford (Box B)
    - Basom, Fred (Box B)
    - Bathija, Jyoti (Box B)
    - Beardon, L.S. (Box B)
    - Bell, Dominick (Box B)
    - Belshaw, Doris (Box B)
    - Benner, Mark (Box B)
    - Birnbaum, Aaron (Box B)
  - (Box 62)
    - Bosley, Tyrone (Box C)
    - Brackfeld, Susan (Washburn) (Box C)
    - Broadus, Raymond (Box C)
    - Brice, Freddie (Box C)
    - Browne, Berkley (Box C)
    - Burger, Robert (Box C)
    - Burnett, Ty (Box C)
    - Burt, Dave (Box C)
    - Burwell, Vernon (Box C)
    - Byron, Archie (Box C)
    - Chavez, David Cervantez (Box C)
    - Cipri, Phil (Box C)
    - Cipri, Ray (Box C)
    - Cipriani Brothers (Box C)
    - Clark, Larry (Box C)
    - Coins, Raymond (Box C)
    - Conlon, Phil (Box C)
    - Cooper, W. A. (Box C)
    - Cosby, Elaine (Box C)
    - Cotrona, George (Box C)
  - (Box 62)
    - Cotrona, George (Cont.) (Box D)
    - Craven, Richard (Box D)
    - Crain, James (Box D)
    - Danek, Karolina (Box D)
  - (Box 62)
    - Danek, Karolina (cont.) (Box E)
    - Daniels, Spot (Box E)
    - Danoff, Soloman (Box E)
    - Darling, Sanford (Box E)
    - Davis, Doris (Box E)
  - (Box 62)
    - Davis, Vestie (Box F)
    - Del Rio, Jose (Box F)
    - Dial, Mattie (Box F)
    - Dial Thorton (Box F)
    - Digney, Jerry (Box F)
    - Dowler, Danny (Box F)
  - (Box 62)
    - Dowler, Danny (cont.) (Box G)
    - Drucker, Harry (Box G)
    - Duany, Diane (Box G)
    - Dunn, Mamie (Box G)
    - Earl, Gary (Box G)
    - Easterwood, Russell (Box G)
    - Elf, Shari (Box G)
    - Erath, Paul (Box G)
    - Evans, Don (Box G)
    - Ewen, Kai (Box G)
    - Ferrario, Paola (Box G)
    - Fire, Irene (Box G)
  - (Box 62)
    - Fire, Irene (cont.) (Box H)
    - Foster, Ben (Box H)
    - Foster, Rene (Box H)
    - Fox, Mara (Box H)
    - Free-man, Sandy Boe (Box H)
    - Fregoso, Sylvia (Box H)
    - Fuller, Leon (Box H)
- Photographs
  - (Box 63)
    - Gibbs, Don (Box A)
    - Gipson, Sybil (Box A)
    - Gilpin, Robert (Box A)
    - Goldman, Gale (Box A)
    - Gordon, Mary (Box A)
    - Green, Homer (Box A)
  - (Box 63)
    - Homer, Green (Cont.) (Box B)
    - Grice, Eddie (Box B)
    - Grisham, Skip (Box B)
    - Hadin, Chris (Box B)
    - Hall, Dilmus (Box B)
    - Hamilton, Ray (Box B)
    - Hammersmith (Box B)
    - Hardin, Joe (Box B)
    - Harris, Ben (Box B)
    - Harvey, Bessie (Box B)
    - Hawkins, William (Box B)
    - Hayes, Richard (Box B)
    - Haynes, Sam (Box B)
    - Hennessy, Heidi (Box B)
    - Hernandez, Jorge (Box B)
    - Hill, Theodore (Box B)
    - Holden, Mike (Box B)
  - (Box 63)
    - Holley, Lonny (Box C)
    - Holmes, Juliet (Box C)
    - Howard, Jesse (Box C)
    - Hudson, Walter Tiree (Box C)
    - Jackson, Tisha (Box C)
    - Jackson, Vincent (Box C)
    - Jarrett, Alvin (Box C)
  - (Box 63)
    - Jennings, James Harold (Box D)
    - Jones, Clyde (Box D)
    - Jordan, John (Box D)
  - (Box 63)
    - Jordan, John (cont.) (Box E)
  - (Box 63)
    - Jordan, John (cont.) (Box F)
    - Jordon, Pia (Box F)
    - Kahn, Samuel (Box F)
    - Kane, Andy (Box F)
    - Keller, Karl (Box F)
    - Kennedy (Box F)
    - Killion, Helene (Box F)
    - Krasner, Ann (Box F)
    - Laga, William (Box F)
    - Langrock, David (Box F)
  - (Box 63)
    - Langrock, David (cont.) (Box G)
    - Larson, Lennert (Box G)
    - Leeds, Eileen (Box G)
    - Lenoir, A. (Box G)
    - Lewis, Karamaya (Box G)
    - Librizzi, Ray (Box G)
  - (Box 63)
    - Light Family (Box H)
    - Linkus, Mark (Box H)
    - Livingston, Calvin (Box H)
    - Lloyd, Winnie (Box H)
    - Low, Cynthia (Box H)
- Photographs
  - (Box 64)
    - Low, Cynthia (cont.) (Box A)
    - Lucas, Charlie (Box A)
    - Lynch, Kenneth (Box A)
    - Marinko, George (Box A)
    - Mark, Stephie (Box A)
    - Maurer, Rolf (Box A)
    - Mayes, Harrison (Box A)
    - McCarthy, Justin (Box A)
  - (Box 64)
    - McCarthy, Justin (cont.) (Box B)
    - McKay, Kenny (Box B)
    - McNellis, Laura Craig (Box B)
    - McNulty, James (Box B)
    - Meyer, C. (Box B)
    - Middleton, Ralph (Box B)
    - Miettinen, Tyyne (Box B)
    - Mitchell, LeRoy (Box B)
    - Morrow, Patty (Box B)
    - Montique, Shalimar (Box B)
    - Mobarak (Box B)
    - Morse, Bruce (Box B)
  - (Box 64)
    - Morse, Bruce (cont.) (Box C)
  - (Box 64)
    - Morse, Bruce (cont.) (Box D)
    - Mumma, Eddy (Box D)
    - Nemoitin, Jacob (Box D)
  - (Box 64)
    - Nemoitin, Jacob (cont.) (Box E)
    - North, H. C. (Box E)
    - Opal, Christine Marie (Box E)
    - PAE (Box E)
    - Pardo, Rosie (Box E)
    - Parschall (Box E)
    - Pawlovsky, Ellia (Box E)
    - Perkins, B. F. (Box E)
    - Perry, Eugene (Box E)
    - Peterson, Leonard (Box E)
    - Pfriender, Pops (Box E)
    - Phillips, Irene (Box E)
    - Pierce, Warren (Box E)
    - Polan, Michele (Box E)
  - (Box 64)
    - Preisser, Ella (Box F)
    - Prince, Dan (Box F)
  - (Box 64)
    - Prince, Dan (cont.) (Box G)
    - Prince, Harold (Box G)
    - Quatch, Cam (Box G)
    - Rabinov, Irwin (Box G)
    - Ray, Jefferey D. (Box G)
    - Reed, Popeye (Box G)
    - Rembert (Box G)
    - Richard, Deveron (Box G)
    - Roberg, Robert (Box G)
    - Rogers, Juanita (Box G)
  - (Box 64)
    - Romano, Joe (Box H)
    - Rosen, Seymour (Box H)
    - Ross, Alex (Box H)
    - Ryan, Stephen (Box H)
- Photographs
  - (Box 65)
    - Ryan, Stephen (cont.) (Box A)
    - S., Ted (Box A)
    - Salvatore, Joseph Anthony (Tony Joe) (Box A)
    - Santaliz, Pauline (Box A)
    - Saussy, CiCi (Box A)
    - Schafle, Kristy (Box A)
    - Schatz, Bernard (L-15) (Box A)
  - (Box 65)
    - Schatz, Bernard (L-15) (cont.) (Box B)
    - Schuss, Kerry (Box B)
    - Scruggs, Mary B. (Box B)
    - Secon, David (Box B)
  - (Box 65)
    - Secon, David (cont.) (Box C)
    - Secq, Caroline (Box C)
  - (Box 65)
    - Secq, Caroline (cont.) (Box D)
    - Segal, Roy (Box D)
    - Serl, Jon (Box D)
    - Shanahan, Jim (Box D)